[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a woman has these pains, they almost always disappear when she becomes pregnant.", "correct_answer": "Arthritic pains", "incorrect_answers": ["Stomach aches", "Neural pains", "Migraine pains"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the author of The Asian Saga, a series of six epic novels centering on Europeans in Asia.", "correct_answer": "James Clavell", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry James", "James White", "James Joyce"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the age of most non-synthetic diamonds.", "correct_answer": "Over three billion years", "incorrect_answers": ["Over seven billion years", "Over five billion years", "Over six billion years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Raspberries are especially high in this vitamin.", "correct_answer": "Vitamin C", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin D", "Vitamin K", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed James Bond in the 2008 spy movie Quantum of Solace, one of the priciest movies in history?", "correct_answer": "Daniel Craig", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Timothy Dalton", "Pierce Brosnan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name Moroccos capital that is also the capital of the Rabat-Sal\u00e9-Zemmour-Zaer region.", "correct_answer": "Rabat", "incorrect_answers": ["Casablanca", "Pretoria", "Niamey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sport is the subject of the 1986 movie Hoosiers, ranked the 4th best sports movie by the American Film Institute?", "correct_answer": "Basketball", "incorrect_answers": ["Baseball", "Rugby", "Football"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In November of 2002 Sprint PCS announced the launch of the first US camera phone.  Who was the manufacturer?", "correct_answer": "Sanyo", "incorrect_answers": ["Nokia", "LG", "Siemens"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal translation of the Greek word amphibios, from which the modern word amphibian originated?", "correct_answer": "Both kinds of life", "incorrect_answers": ["Water and land", "Two in one", "Water and air"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did the first episode of the unforgettable Mr. Bean premiere on ITV channel (changed to Channel 3 soon after)?", "correct_answer": "January 1, 1990", "incorrect_answers": ["May 1, 1990", "September 1, 1992", "February 13, 1989"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Pacific lobster has large pincers and a spiny shell.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first food to be microwaved?", "correct_answer": "A candy bar", "incorrect_answers": ["Popcorn", "Coffee", "Frozen corn"]}]